

[Nur Isnaini]

Purwokerto, Central Java, 53145 | +62 856 4337 0496 | nurisnaini2605@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/nur-isnaini | www.instagram.com/nurisnaini | http://bit.ly/nurisnainiportfolio

About Me

I'm Nur Isnaini, Bachelor Communications Science, Jenderal Soedirman University 2019. Have experiences as a Radio Announcer, TV Host, Production, MC, and Business Development on PT Shopee International Indonesia with achievement **A** (79%/100%). I'm a fast learner. I have a career interest in Business Development, Broadcasting or Creative Team and I'm good at using Cool Edit Pro, Adobe Premiere Pro, and Google Spreadsheet.

Skill and Competence

- Microsoft Excel/Google Spreadsheet
- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Photoshop & Premiere Pro
- Detail Oriented
- Cool Edit Pro
- Public Speaking

Work Experience

PT Shopee International Indonesia (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Relationship Manager, Business Development Analyst (November 2019-March 2021)

- Responsible for manage around 100 sellers and develop Shopee's business with partners on the Shopee platform also educate Managed Sellers to increase the efficiency of using the Shopee platform in business
- Work Achievement: There was an increase in Shopee's business and Shopee's seller partners, awareness from sellers about the features and programs available on the Shopee platform, had a point A on KPI

Resivi.id (Jawa Tengah, Indonesia)

Voice Over Talent Freelance (August 2016-October 2019)

As a talent for audio material

Satelit TV Purwokerto (Jawa Tengah, Indonesia)

Host of Dialog Interaktif Program (May 2019-October 2019)

• Responsible for guiding interactive programs with interviewees and viewers

PT Radio Suara Banyumas Aseli, Sonora FM Purwokerto (Jawa Tengah, Indonesia)

Radio Announcer (August 2016-February 2019)

• Responsible for preparing and guiding radio program programs

Producer (January 2018-February 2019)

 Responsible for producing on air programs also audio materials for programs and advertisements

Music Director (August 2017-February 2019)

Responsible for managing music for on air program playlists

Meotel Hotel Purwokerto by Dafam (Jawa Tengah, Indonesia)

Guest Relations Officer Apprentice (September 2018-November 2018)

• Responsible for provide required information for hotel executive guests

Education

Formal

Jenderal Soedirman University (2015-2019)

Bachelor Communications Studies - GPA 3.86

- Head of Advocacy and Studies Division of Communication Science Student Association in 2017
- Staff Research and Development Division of Communication Science Student Association in 2016

SMAN 2 Purwokerto (2012-2015)

Social Science Major

- Head of Community Service at Ambalan Garuda-Shima on 2013
- As a Banyumas Contingent on 2013 and did the General Champion in Central Java Scouting Competition

Non Formal

Taeyang Kulture (2020-Now)

Korean: Level 1B

ELTI Gramedia (2015)

English: Active Communication

Achievement

Jenderal Soedirman University (December 2017)

Best Public Service Advertisement: Lindungi Buruh Migran

• As a Director and Voice Over Talent

Contact References

Mr. Grytje Gregory Handiwono, Station Manager

PT Radio Suara Banyumas Aseli (Sonora FM Purwokerto)

+62 816-859-535